vmagazine.com 2008-02-07

# V MAGAZINE | PRIVACY POLICY

**_V_ Magazine Privacy Policy and Legal Notice**

At _V_ Magazine, we are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy and Legal Notice will advise you about how we protect your personal information, what choices you have concerning the use of that information, your legal rights as a copyright owner, and other pertinent legal information.

 **The Information We Collect and How We Use It**

We collect information on the site in order to make it possible for you to access all the features on our site and to enhance your overall experience on our site. You can browse our site without submitting any personally identifiable information, but we do collect some anonymous information when you access our site.  
 **  
Information Provided by You**

When you visit our site, you will be invited to provide personal information to purchase an issue or subscription, or [to join our mailing list]. To purchase an issue or subscription, you will be asked for your name, billing and shipping addresses, e-mail address, credit card number and credit card expiration date. [To join our mailing list, you will be asked for your e-mail address only].  

 **Information Shared With Third Parties**

We may use your contact data to send you information about _V_ Magazine. You may always opt out of receiving future mailings (see the “Opt Out” section below).

In addition, we may employ outside agents, meaning other companies or individuals to perform functions on our behalf, such as sending postal mail and e-mail, conducting sweepstakes and other promotional activities, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. These _V_ Magazine agents have access to personal information needed to perform their functions. Other than our outside agents and certain _V_ Magazine suppliers and vendors, we keep all of your personal information private and will not share it with any third party, unless you have authorized us to or we are legally required to do so. _V_ Magazine may also release personal information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to protect the rights, property or safety of _V_ Magazine, our users, or others.

 **Security of Your Information**

When you purchase an issue or subscription online, we need to obtain your credit card number, expiration date, and billing and shipping address information. This information is encrypted and transmitted over the Internet where it is stored securely at _V_ Magazine and used for billing purposes only.

Our site has security measures in place intended to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. _V_ Magazine uses industry standard encryption to help ensure that all the personal information you provide is encrypted and remains private. This helps to maintain the confidentiality of your information.

We strive to protect your personal information, however, _V_ Magazine cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us.

 **Correcting or Updating Personal Information**

If your personal information changes, we will gladly correct, update, or remove any data you have previously provided to us. You may change your personal information at any time by sending _V_ Magazine an e-mail at info@vmagazine.com. We may retain a copy of the prior version for our records.

 **Opt Out**

 _V_ Magazine may send users news about new offerings and special projects. To help us make e-mails more useful and interesting, we may receive a confirmation when you open e-mail from _V_ Magazine.  You may choose to opt out of receiving such mailings by sending us a “Please remove” e-mail message to info@vmagazine.com.

 **Demographic Information**

Demographic and profile data may be collected at our site. _V_ Magazine may provide such information in the aggregate to third parties without disclosure of personally identifying information.

 **IP Address**

We automatically track IP (internet protocol) addresses for statistical purposes. IP addresses are logged per user’s session and help to determine how often areas on our site are visited. _V_ Magazine does not track IP addresses with any of your personal information, so we will never link an IP address to a specific user. We also monitor traffic patterns and site usage to help us develop and improve the design and layout of the site.

 **Cookies**

We use cookies to improve your experience at _V_ Magazine. “Cookies” are small pieces of information that a website transfers to your computer’s hard drive for record-keeping purposes. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user’s computer. We use cookies to remember information users give us so they don’t have to reenter it each time they visit our site. You are always free to decline our cookies if your browser permits. Even without a cookie, you will still be able to use most of the features on our site.

 **Copyright Notice**

All text, images, graphics, sounds, and software code (“Content”) on this site are copyrighted property of _V_ Magazine, its contributors, and its programmers unless otherwise noted. They may only be used for the personal education of site visitors. They may not be placed in the public domain. You may not reproduce, redistribute, publish, or otherwise use by electronic or any other means any of the Content without our prior written consent.

 **Trademarks**

 _V_ Magazine and other marks indicated on our site are service marks of _V_ Magazine.  They may not be used or displayed without the prior written consent of _V_ Magazine.  All other trademarks, product names, and company names and logos appearing on the site are the property of their respective owners.

 **Applicable Law**

These terms will be governed by and construed in accordance with the laws of the State of New York, without regard to any principles of conflicts of law. You agree that any action at law or in equity that arises out of or relates to any use of the _V_ Magazine site will be filed only in the state or federal courts located in New York County, and you hereby consent and submit to the personal jurisdiction of such courts for the purposes of litigating any such action.

 **Your Acceptance of These Terms**

By visiting the _V_ Magazine site, you consent to the terms of this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice and to the collection and use of this information by _V_ Magazine. We will always fully disclose our privacy policies, and we will promptly post any changes to our policy on this page.

You agree that _V_ Magazine may retain and use your personal information as described in this policy until you inform us that you do not agree with this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice and agree that you will not use the _V_ Magazine site for a reasonable period of time thereafter. By using this site after we post any changes to this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice, you agree to accept those changes.

If you choose to visit _V_ Magazine, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and Legal Notice.

 **Contacting the Website**

If you have any questions about this privacy and legal notice statement, the practices of this site, or your interactions with this website, you may contact:

V Magazine  
ATTN: vmagazine.com   
11 Mercer Street   
New York, NY 10013  
USA

E-mail: info@vmagazine.com
